Guide to Records of the Office of the President (John Brademas) RG.3.0.10
New York University Archives
- Series XIII. Speeches and Writings, 1981-1991; 22.50 Linear Feet in 54 manuscript boxes.; 1 audiocassette; 3 VHS
  - Graduate School of Arts and Science 100th Anniversary Convocation (NYU), 1986-11-19 (Box 281, Folder 5)
  - Introducing Honorary Degree Recipients at a Dinner Honoring the 100th Anniversary of the Graduate School of Arts and Science (NYU), 1986-11-19 (Box 281, Folder 6)
  - "Tax Reform in America: The Impact on Higher Education," 15th Annual Business Symposium Sponsored by St. Peter's College (Jersey City, NJ), 1986-11-19 (Box 281, Folder 7)
  - School of Business and Public Administration and Graduate School Board of Overseers Meeting RESTRICTED, 1986-11-20 (Box 103, Folder 16)
  - John Douglas Scanlan Dinner, 1986-11-25 (Box 281, Folder 8)
  - Neil Gordon Kinnock Dinner (NYU), 1986-12-01 (Box 281, Folder 9)
  - New York Times President's Forum (New York, NY), 1986-12-02 (Box 281, Folder 10)
  - Humanities Council 10th Anniversary Lecture, Saul Bellow Introduction (NYU), 1986-12-04 (Box 281, Folder 11)
  - Sports and Recreation Development Committee Meeting (NYU), 1986-12-05 (Box 281, Folder 12)
  - Board of Trustees Meeting (NYU) RESTRICTED, 1986-12-08 (Box 103, Folder 17)
  - Essay Re: Federal Support for Higher Education for Scholarship and Public Policy -- Humanities Council, 1986-12-09 (Box 281, Folder 13)
  - University Senate Meeting (NYU), 1986-12-11 (Box 281, Folder 14)
  - Department of Hebrew and Judaic Studies Dinner (NYU), 1986-12-11 (Box 281, Folder 15)
  - New York Times Interview Re: Claire Flom and the Alliance, 1986-12-11 (Box 281, Folder 16)
  - "Meanwhile Greece Goes on Traveling…", Nicholas E. Christopher Memorial Lecture in Modern Greek Studies (Cambridge, MA), 1986-12-12 (Box 281, Folder 17)
  - Dinner Honoring Major Donors (NYU), 1986-12-16 (Box 281, Folder 18)
  - NYU Faculty Council, 1986-12-18 (Box 281, Folder 19)
  - "Scholarship and Public Policy", New York Public Library Lecture (New York, NY), 1987-01-06 (Box 281, Folder 20)
  - NYU Medical Center Board of Trustees RESTRICTED, 1987-01-06 (Box 103, Folder 18)
  - Highlights of the NYU Presidency of John Brademas, 1987-01-10 (Box 281, Folder 21)
  - Op-Ed Response to Forbes Magazine Article by Peter Brimelow, 1987-01-23 (Box 281, Folder 22)
  - Sigma Xi of Terre Haute Reception (Terre Haute, IN), 1987-01-26 (Box 281, Folder 23)
  - "Scholarship of Public Policy" University Speaker Series (Terre Haute, IN), 1987-01-26 (Box 281, Folder 24)
  - Presidential Message for NYU Staff Handbook, 1987-01-27 (Box 281, Folder 25)
  - "The Role of Congress in Foreign Policy: Reflections of a Former Congressman", Indiana State University (Terre Haute, IN), 1987-01-27 (Box 281, Folder 26)
  - Indiana State University Founders Day Ceremony (Terre Haute, IN), 1987-01-27 (Box 281, Folder 27)
  - Institute of Fine Arts Board Meeting RESTRICTED, 1987-01-28 (Box 103, Folder 19)
  - National Book Critics Circle Awards Ceremony (NYU), 1987-01-29 (Box 281, Folder 28)
  - WABC Talk Radio "Reach for Speech" Show Interview (New York, NY), 1987-02-01 (Box 281, Folder 29)
  - Journal of International Law and Politics Symposium: Trade Sanctions and International Relations (NYU), 1987-02-05 (Box 281, Folder 30)
  - "National Priorities in Higher Education," National Association of Independent Colleges and Universities Annual Meeting (Washington, D.C.), 1987-02-06 (Box 282, Folder 1)
  - Executive Committee Meeting RESTRICTED, 1987-02-09 (Box 103, Folder 20)
  - Testimony, Hearing of the Committee on Education and Labor (Washington, D.C.), 1987-02-10 (Box 282, Folder 2)
  - Oxford Piece -- NYU Report, 1987-02-11 (Box 282, Folder 3)
  - University Senate Meeting (NYU), 1987-02-12 (Box 282, Folder 4)
  - Citizens Committee, New Yorker for New York Awards (New York, NY), 1987-02-12 (Box 282, Folder 5)
  - "Is the Agenda for Science too Important to be Left to Scientists?" Sigma Xi Article for American Scientist, 1987-02-15 (Box 282, Folder 6)
  - Anti-Drug Effort, Washington Square Park, 1987-02-17 (Box 282, Folder 7)
  - Consulate-General of the People's Republic of China (New York, NY), 1987-02-17 (Box 282, Folder 8)
  - Democratic National Committee National Finance Council Winter Meeting (Newport Beach, CA), 1987-02-21 (Box 282, Folder 9)
  - NYU AIDS Mental Health Project Press Conference (NYU), 1987-02-24 (Box 282, Folder 10)
  - Lecture by Giovanni Spadolini, NYU Law School, 1987-02-25 (Box 282, Folder 11)
  - 2nd Annual Petrie Lecture in Entrepreneurship and Dinner (NYU), 1987-02-26 (Box 282, Folder 12)
  - "International Education: A Matter of Survival," Article for Education Record, 1987-02-27 (Box 282, Folder 13)
  - University Article by Brademas on Oxford, England, 1987-03 (Box 282, Folder 14)
  - Lunch for Peter Lax (NYU), 1987-03-03 (Box 282, Folder 15)
  - Medical Center Board Meeting RESTRICTED, 1987-03-04 (Box 103, Folder 21)
  - Dinner for Trustees, Deans, Faculty and Administration Hosted by David Kriser (NYU), 1987-03-04 (Box 282, Folder 16)
  - Scholars Day (NYU), 1987-03-08 (Box 282, Folder 17)
  - Afternoon at Washington Square (NYU), 1987-03-08 (Box 282, Folder 18)
  - NYU in Albany Reception (Albany, NY), 1987-03-09 (Box 282, Folder 19)
  - NYU in Albany Alumni Reception (Albany, NY), 1987-03-09 (Box 282, Folder 20)
  - Trustee Financial Meeting RESTRICTED, 1987-03-09 (Box 103, Folder 22)
  - Presidential, University and Educational Scholars Breakfast (NYU), 1987-03-10 (Box 282, Folder 21)
  - Metro Center Benefit Luncheon (NYU), 1987-03-10 (Box 282, Folder 22)
  - "NYU: University in the City," New-York Historical Society (New York, NY), 1987-03-11 (Box 282, Folder 23)
  - University Senate Meeting (NYU), 1987-03-12 (Box 282, Folder 24)
  - "Modern Role of Congress," Association of the Bar Forum (New York, NY), 1987-03-12 (Box 282, Folder 25)
  - Board of Trustees Meeting RESTRICTED, 1987-03-16 (Box 103, Folder 23)
  - Introduction of Mario Cuomo at Arms Control Forum (NYU), 1987-03-16 (Box 282, Folder 26)
  - Press Conference for "Due Case, Una Tradizione" Project (NYU), 1987-03-16 (Box 282, Folder 27)
  - Graduate School of Public Administration Dean's Day (NYU), 1987-03-16 (Box 282, Folder 28)
  - Lynne Cheney Press Luncheon and Dinner (NYU), 1987-03-16 (Box 282, Folder 29)
  - Dinner Honoring Lady Mary Warnock (NYU), 1987-03-17 (Box 282, Folder 30)
  - Real Estate Institute Urban Leadership Award Dinner (NYU), 1987-03-18 (Box 282, Folder 31)
  - Hoosiers Movie Dinner (NYU), 1987-03-19 (Box 282, Folder 32)
  - Chicago Alumni Reception, 1987-03-26 (Box 283, Folder 1)
  - Meetings with Alumni in Chicago and Los Angeles, 1987-03-26-1987-03-29 (Box 283, Folder 2)
  - Onassis Center for Hellenic Studies -- Convocation Materials (NYU), 1987-03-30 (Box 283, Folder 3)
  - Onassis Center For Hellenic Studies Press Conference and Dinner (NYU), 1987-03-30 (Box 283, Folder 4)
  - Onassis Center for Hellenic Studies Announcement, Convocation (NYU), 1987-03-30 (Box 101, Video 35)
  - Gallatin 15th Anniversary Dinner (NYU), 1987-03-31 (Box 283, Folder 5)
  - "Scholarships and Public Policy," Essay for Book on the Humanities, 1987-04-01 (Box 283, Folder 6)
  - NY Science Policy Association (New York, NY), 1987-04-01 (Box 283, Folder 7)
  - Testimony Before Committee on Governmental Affairs (Washington, D.C.), 1987-04-02 (Box 283, Folder 8)
  - New England Alumni Brunch (Boston, MA), 1987-04-05 (Box 283, Folder 9)
  - Dinner Honoring and Lecture by Gerald Aylmer (NYU), 1987-04-06 (Box 283, Folder 10)
  - American Council on Education (ACE) Government Relations - Review Letter, 1987-04-07 (Box 283, Folder 11)
  - University Senate Meeting (NYU), 1987-04-09 (Box 283, Folder 12)
  - Stephen J., Sr. and Beatrice Brademas Lecture (Muncie, IN), 1987-04-13 (Box 283, Folder 13)
  - Greek Fulbright Alumni Association (Athens, Greece), 1987-04-28 (Box 283, Folder 14)
  - "Fulbright at 40: Forging the Ties that Bind," Fulbright Distinguished Fellows Lecture (Greece), 1987-04-29 (Box 283, Folder 15)
  - Dinner Honoring the American School of Classical Studies (Greece), 1987-04-30 (Box 283, Folder 16)
  - "Message from the President," Staff and Faculty Handbook (NYU), 1987-05-04 (Box 283, Folder 17)
  - Celebration of the 150th Anniversary of the National and Capodistrian University of Athens (Athens, Greece), 1987-05-04 (Box 283, Folder 18)
  - "Facing the Competition in Brainpower" Address, 20th Annual Conference on the New York City Economy, 1987-05-06 (Box 283, Folder 19)
  - Institute of Fine Arts Board Meeting RESTRICTED, 1987-05-06 (Box 102, Folder 1)
  - Notre Dame Alumni Club of New York Dinner (New York, NY), 1987-05-06 (Box 283, Folder 20)
  - President's Council Reception (NYU), 1987-05-07 (Box 283, Folder 21)
  - Notre Dame Speech, 1987-05-09 (Box 283, Folder 22)
  - Board of Trustees Meeting RESTRICTED, 1987-05-11 (Box 102, Folder 2)
  - Dedication of the Paulette Goddard Staircase, Tisch School of the Arts (NYU), 1987-05-11 (Box 283, Folder 23)
  - Dinner Celebrating the Tisch School of the Arts (NYU), 1987-05-11 (Box 283, Folder 24)
  - New York Academy of Public Education (New York University Club), 1987-05-12 (Box 283, Folder 25)
  - Tenth Anniversary of Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives Dinner (NYU), 1987-05-13 (Box 283, Folder 26)
  - University Senate Meeting (NYU), 1987-05-14 (Box 283, Folder 27)
  - Leonard Stern Hall Dedication (NYU), 1987-05-14 (Box 283, Folder 28)
  - Humanities Council Symposium (NYU), 1987-05-15 (Box 284, Folder 1)
  - Washington D.C. Alumni Brunch, 1987-05-17 (Box 284, Folder 2)
  - Bobst Awards in Arts and Letters (NYU), 1987-05-19 (Box 284, Folder 3)
  - King Juan Carlos I Chair in Spanish Culture, 1987-05-20 (Box 284, Folder 4)
  - 25-Year Service Awards (NYU), 1987-05-20 (Box 284, Folder 5)
  - NYU Community Fund Check Presentations (NYU), 1987-05-21 (Box 284, Folder 6)
  - Gallatin Association Leadership Breakfast (New York, NY), 1985-05-27 (Box 284, Folder 7)
  - Alumni Council Annual Meeting (NYU), 1987-05-28 (Box 284, Folder 8)
  - Walter Nichols Award to James D. Robinson III (NYU), 1987-05-29 (Box 284, Folder 9)
  - United Jewish Appeal - 2nd Annual Meeting of Council of Overseers (New York, NY), 1987-06-01 (Box 284, Folder 10)
  - Graduate School of Business Administration Pre-Commencement Remarks (New York, NY), 1987-06-02 (Box 284, Folder 11)
  - Medical Center Board of Trustees Meeting RESTRICTED, 1987-06-02 (Box 102, Folder 3)
  - New York Congressional Delegation (Washington, D.C.), 1987-06-03 (Box 284, Folder 12)
  - Educational Press Association of American Annual Meeting (Washington, D.C.), 1987-06-04 (Box 284, Folder 13)
  - Trustees Pre-Commencement Dinner Remarks (NYU), 1987-06-04 (Box 284, Folder 14)
  - Alumni Commencement Breakfast (NYU), 1987-06-05 (Box 284, Folder 15)
  - 155th NYU Commencement, 1987-06-05 (Box 284, Folder 16)
  - School of Business and Public Administration Entrepreneur of the Year Award Dinner (New York, NY), 1987-06-06 (Box 284, Folder 17)
  - Ninth Annual National Hospitality Industry Investment Conference (New York, NY), 1987-06-09 (Box 284, Folder 18)
  - Abraham Gitlow Chair in Business Administration Reception (NYU), 1987-06-10 (Box 284, Folder 19)
  - Acceptance of Honorary Degree at University of Athens (Athens, Greece), 1987-06-12 (Box 284, Folder 20)
  - Tribute to Arthur M. Sackler, Metropolitan Museum of Art (New York, NY), 1987-06-17 (Box 284, Folder 21)
  - Ecumenical Doxology Celebration of Independence Day Homily, St. Bartholomew Church (New York, NY), 1987-07-04 (Box 284, Folder 22)
  - "Congress and American Foreign Policy: The Lessons of Irangate," Atlantic Institute for International Affairs (Paris, France), 1987-07-06 (Box 284, Folder 23)
  - Jefferson-Jackson Day Dinner (Indianapolis, IN), 1987-07-28 (Box 284, Folder 24)
  - Article in the American Scientist, 1987-07-30 (Box 284, Folder 25)
  - Tribute to Joseph E. Levine (New York, NY), 1987-08-03 (Box 284, Folder 26)
  - Encyclopedia of New York City Endorsement, 1987-08-14 (Box 284, Folder 27)
  - Article Re: Fulbright Distinguished Fellows for PS Magazine, 1987-08-31 (Box 284, Folder 28)
  - New Student Convocation (NYU), 1987-09-14 (Box 284, Folder 29)
  - Inauguration of Chancellor Ismar Schorsch, Jewish Theological Seminary (New York, NY), 1987-09-14 (Box 284, Folder 30)
  - Panel Discussion on the Bicentennial of the Constitution, Center for Strategic and International Studies (Washington, D.C.), 1987-09-15 (Box 285, Folder 1)
  - Remarks on the Role of Congress in American Foreign Policy, National Council of Jewish Women (New York, NY), 1987-09-17 (Box 285, Folder 2)
  - Remarks on Higher Education, Convocation at Clark University (Worcester, MA), 1987-09-18 (Box 285, Folder 3)
  - Remarks on Leisure, Society of Park and Recreation Educators (New Orleans, LA), 1987-09-20 (Box 285, Folder 4)
  - Welcome Back Party for Vice Presidents, Deans and VIPs (NYU), 1987-09-21 (Box 285, Folder 5)
  - Board of Trustees Meeting (NYU) RESTRICTED, 1987-09-21 (Box 102, Folder 4)
  - "Doxology About Greek Heritage and the U.S. Constitution", Greek Orthodox Archdiocesan Cathedral of the Holy Trinity (New York, NY), 1987-09-27 (Box 285, Folder 6)
  - Luncheon Honoring Wu Xueqian, Chinese Minister of Foreign Affairs, Council on Foreign Relations (New York, NY), 1987-09-29 (Box 285, Folder 7)
  - Luncheon for Marian Orzechowski, Foreign Minister of Poland (NYU), 1987-09-30 (Box 285, Folder 8)
  - New York Observer Article on the Importance of NYU to Manhattan, 1987-10-05 (Box 285, Folder 9)
  - NYU Medical Center Board Meeting RESTRICTED, 1987-10-06 (Box 102, Folder 5)
  - Script for Methodist Television Show "Catch the Spirit" Taping (NYU), 1987-10-06 (Box 285, Folder 10)
  - Reception for New Graduate Students (NYU), 1987-10-06 (Box 285, Folder 11)
  - Remarks on the School of Business and Public Administration, Charles Waldo Haskins Award Dinner (New York, NY), 1987-10-07 (Box 285, Folder 12)
  - Introduction for Book, Group Portrait by Sven Groenning, 1987-10-07 (Box 285, Folder 13)
  - University Senate Meeting (NYU), 1987-10-08 (Box 285, Folder 14)
  - Institute of French Studies Conference (NYU), 1987-10-09 (Box 285, Folder 15)
  - Remarks on the Role of Congress in American Foreign Policy, Iona College Fall Honors Convocation (New Rochelle, NY), 1987-10-18 (Box 285, Folder 16)
  - Breakfast for NYU Orientation Leaders (NYU), 1987-10-19 (Box 285, Folder 17)
  - Board of Trustees Meeting RESTRICTED, 1987-10-19 (Box 102, Folder 6)
  - Graduate School of Business Administration Overseers' Dinner (NYU), 1987-10-19 (Box 285, Folder 18)
  - Alumni Campaign Kickoff Breakfast (NYU), 1987-10-20 (Box 285, Folder 19)
  - Remarks on Learned Societies, American Antiquarian Society 175th Anniversary (Worcester, MA), 1987-10-21 (Box 285, Folder 20)
  - All-University Convocation (NYU), 1987-10-22 (Box 285, Folder 21)
  - New York State School Boards Association Annual Convention (Albany, NY), 1987-10-23 (Box 285, Folder 22)
  - College of Business and Public Administration Dean's Day (NYU), 1987-10-24 (Box 285, Folder 23)
  - Phi Beta Kappa Associates Annual Awards Dinner (New York, NY), 1987-10-24 (Box 285, Folder 24)
  - Faculty of Arts and Science Newsletter, 1987-10-27 (Box 285, Folder 25)
  - National Broadcasting Seminar for Foreign Journalists (NYU), 1987-10-27 (Box 285, Folder 26)
  - Graduate School of Business Administration Annual Awards Dinner (New York, NY), 1987-10-27 (Box 285, Folder 27)
  - 40th Anniversary of the Institute of Environmental Medicine, NYU Medical Center, 1987-10-29 (Box 285, Folder 28)
  - Carnegie Council on Ethics and International Affairs "Worldview Breakfast" (New York, NY), 1987-10-30 (Box 285, Folder 29)
  - Metro Center Press Conference (NYU), 1987-11-02 (Box 285, Folder 30)
  - Quote for Terrel Bell Book, 1987-11-02 (Box 285, Folder 31)
  - Institute of Fine Arts Board Meeting RESTRICTED, 1987-11-04 (Box 102, Folder 7)
  - Parents' Day Receptions for BPA, SEHNAP, TSOA, CAS, SCE/GSP (NYU), 1987-11-08 (Box 285, Folder 32)
  - Women's Forum (NYU), 1987-11-09 (Box 285, Folder 33)
  - Saul Farber and Peter Hughes Dinner (NYU), 1987-11-09 (Box 285, Folder 34)
  - University Senate Meeting (NYU), 1987-11-12 (Box 285, Folder 35)
  - Remarks on Arts and Public Policy, Meeting of the Federation of State Humanities Councils (Chicago, IL), 1987-11-14 (Box 286, Folder 1)
  - Indiana University Celebration of the Bicentennial of the Constitution (South Bend, IN), 1987-11-15 (Box 286, Folder 2)
  - "Showcase of Music" Brunch, Indiana University (South Bend, IN), 1987-11-15 (Box 286, Folder 3)
  - Luncheon for New Italian Professorships (NYU), 1987-11-17 (Box 286, Folder 4)
  - Stop-by at Opening of NYU's New Kosher Dining Hall (NYU), 1987-11-18 (Box 286, Folder 5)
  - Trustees Scholars Dinner (NYU), 1987-11-19 (Box 286, Folder 6)
  - Convocation for Kriser Dental Center (NYU), 1987-11-19 (Box 286, Folder 7)
  - Comparative and International Education Society, 1987-11-20 (Box 286, Folder 8)
  - Society of Foreign Consuls (New York, NY), 1987-11-20 (Box 286, Folder 9)
  - Keynote Address, Meeting of the Association for Higher Education (Baltimore, MD), 1987-11-22 (Box 286, Folder 10)
  - Remarks on "The Politics of Education", Harvard Graduate School of Education Seminar (Cambridge, MA), 1987-11-23 (Box 286, Folder 11)
  - "Fourth Estate" Dinner (NYU), 1987-12-02 (Box 286, Folder 12)
  - Executive Committee of the Medical Center Board RESTRICTED, 1987-12-03 (Box 102, Folder 8)
  - The Century Association, Century Club (New York, NY), 1987-12-03 (Box 286, Folder 13)
  - New M.S. Degree in Real Estate at School of Continuing Education Announcement (NYU), 1987-12-07 (Box 286, Folder 14)
  - Board of Trustees Meeting RESTRICTED, 1987-12-07 (Box 102, Folder 9)
  - Dinner at Isabelle Leeds House re: Spain, 1987-12-08 (Box 286, Folder 15)
  - UJA-Federation Proskauer Award Dinner Honoring Arthur L. Linman (New York, NY), 1987-12-09 (Box 286, Folder 16)
  - President's Council Reception (NYU), 1987-12-10 (Box 286, Folder 17)
  - National Education Association / School of Education, Health, Nursing, and the Arts Professions Press Luncheon (NYU), 1987-12-14 (Box 286, Folder 18)
  - Education Week "Commentary" Article, 1987-12-15 (Box 286, Folder 19)
  - Introduction to Lecture by Dr. James Billington (NYU), 1987-12-15 (Box 286, Folder 20)
  - Luncheon for Librarians (NYU), 1987-12-15 (Box 286, Folder 21)
  - Convocation in Praise of Libraries and Librarians (NYU), 1987-12-15 (Box 286, Folder 22)
  - Libraries Dinner (NYU), 1987-12-15 (Box 286, Folder 23)
  - Report to the Faculty Council (NYU), 1987-12-17 (Box 286, Folder 24)
  - Penthouse Dinner for Lord Roy Harris Jenkins Talking Points (NYU), 1988-01-04 (Box 286, Folder 25)
  - Medical Center Board Report RESTRICTED, 1988-01-05 (Box 102, Folder 10)
  - Tribute to Norman Redlich, NYU Law Review, 1988-01-12 (Box 286, Folder 26)
  - Aspen Institute Speech (Berlin, Federal Republic of Germany), 1988-01-12 (Box 286, Folder 27)
  - Remarks on the American System of Government, Royal Institute of International Affairs (London, England), 1988-01-14 (Box 286, Folder 28)
  - Chief Academic Officers Photography Exhibition (NYU), 1988-01-20 (Box 286, Folder 29)
  - Institute of Fine Arts Board Meeting RESTRICTED, 1988-01-27 (Box 102, Folder 11)
  - Remarks on Education, Conference on Teaching of Ethics (Ann Arbor, MI), 1988-01-29 (Box 286, Folder 30)
  - Remarks on Higher Education, Congressional Competitiveness Caucus (Washington, D.C.), 1988-02-02 (Box 287, Folder 1)
  - Remarks on the Role of Higher Education, Association of Catholic Colleges and Universities Annual Meeting (Washington, DC), 1988-02-02 (Box 287, Folder 2)
  - NYU Board of Trustees and Medical Center Board of Trustees Joint Meeting Remarks (Palm Beach, FL) RESTRICTED, 1988-02-06-1988-02-07 (Box 102, Folder 12)
  - University Senate Meeting, 1988-02-11 (Box 287, Folder 3)
  - Education Daily Questionnaire on AIDS, 1988-02-18 (Box 287, Folder 4)
  - Luncheon Honoring Marnold Fellows Program Talking Points (NYU), 1988-02-18 (Box 287, Folder 5)
  - "Due Case, Una Tradizione" Luncheon and Meeting Talking Points (NYU), 1988-02-22 (Box 287, Folder 6)
  - Tribute to Bayly Winder Letter, 1988-02-27 (Box 287, Folder 7)
  - New York University Magazine Prologue, 1988-03 (Box 287, Folder 8)
  - Medical Center Board of Trustees Meeting RESTRICTED, 1988-03-01 (Box 102, Folder 13)
  - Dinner Honoring Charles Lazarus Talking Points (NYU), 1988-03-01 (Box 287, Folder 9)
  - Orton Dyslexia Society Conference (New York, NY), 1988-03-03 (Box 287, Folder 10)
  - Conference Sponsored by Mayor Pascual Maragall Address (Barcelona, Spain), 1988-03-04 (Box 287, Folder 11)
  - Ministry of Education and Science of Spain Seminar (Madrid, Spain), 1988-03-07 (Box 287, Folder 12)
  - Seminar on the Financing of University Research (Madrid, Spain), 1988-03-07 (Box 287, Folder 13)
  - Alumni Council Meeting, Institute of Fine Arts (NYU), 1988-03-09 (Box 287, Folder 14)
  - University Senate Meeting (NYU), 1988-03-10 (Box 287, Folder 15)
  - Global Cities Forum Talking Points (NYU), 1988-03-11 (Box 287, Folder 16)
  - Graduate School of Public Administration Dean's Day (NYU), 1988-03-12 (Box 287, Folder 17)
  - NYU Board of Trustees Meeting RESTRICTED, 1988-03-14 (Box 102, Folder 14)
  - John Carroll Lecture, Georgetown University (Washington, D.C.), 1988-03-15 (Box 287, Folder 18)
  - Humanities Council Lecture Remarks (NYU), 1988-03-16 (Box 287, Folder 19)
  - 21st Annual Real Estate Institute Dinner (New York, NY), 1988-03-16 (Box 287, Folder 20)
  - Dinner Honoring Francis Haskell Talking Points (NYU), 1988-03-17 (Box 287, Folder 21)
  - David Butler Luncheon Seminar (NYU), 1988-03-18 (Box 287, Folder 22)
  - Reception Honoring Eli Evans (NYU), 1988-03-21 (Box 287, Folder 23)
  - Dinner Meeting of the National Academy of Arts and Sciences (NYU), 1988-03-23 (Box 287, Folder 24)
  - Executive Committee Meeting and Luncheon RESTRICTED, 1988-03-29 (Box 102, Folder 15)
  - National Commission on American Foreign Policy (New York, NY), 1988-03-29 (Box 287, Folder 25)
  - Reception Honoring NYU Alumni (Philadelphia, PA), 1988-03-30 (Box 287, Folder 26)
  - Press Conference Announcing the Onassis Center for Hellenic Studies (NYU), 1988-03-30 (Box 287, Folder 27)
  - Luncheon at the Metro Center (NYU), 1988-03-31 (Box 287, Folder 28)
  - Medical Center Board Report RESTRICTED, 1988-04-05 (Box 102, Folder 16)
  - Washington Square Park Clean-up (New York, NY), 1988-04-05 (Box 287, Folder 29)
  - Book Party Sponsored by NYU and the Spanish Institute (NYU), 1988-04-06 (Box 287, Folder 30)
  - Ditchley Foundations Conference (Oxfordshire, England), 1988-04-08-1988-04-10 (Box 287, Folder 31)
  - Down Town Association (New York, NY), 1988-04-20 (Box 287, Folder 32)
  - Executive Committee Report RESTRICTED, 1988-04-20 (Box 102, Folder 17)
  - Congressional Arts Caucus Luncheon (NYU), 1988-04-22 (Box 288, Folder 1)
  - Founders Day Address (NYU), 1988-04-24 (Box 288, Folder 2)
  - Humanities Council Visit Introducing Sir Peter Ramsbotham (NYU), 1988-04-25 (Box 288, Folder 3)
  - Dinner Honoring Sir Peter Ramsbotham (NYU), 1988-04-25 (Box 288, Folder 4)
  - Council on Economic Priorities Dinner (New York, NY), 1988-04-26 (Box 288, Folder 5)
  - Luncheon Announcing the NYU Law and Philanthropy Grant (NYU), 1988-04-27 (Box 288, Folder 6)
  - NYU Family Dinner (New York, NY), 1988-04-27 (Box 288, Folder 7)
  - College of Arts and Science (CASH) Luncheon (NYU), 1988-04-28 (Box 288, Folder 8)
  - Dinner Honoring Mel Miller, 1988-04-28 (Box 288, Folder 9)
  - The James Family and Italy: A Symposium Welcoming Remarks (NYU), 1988-04-29 (Box 288, Folder 10)
  - NYU Spring Celebration Talking Points (NYU), 1988-04-29 (Box 288, Folder 11)